hello hello hello we haven't done one of
these in a while fixing up fly bugs you
know not UI bugs but you I do UI not
happy to talk about all that um yeah
maybe you are 10x faster hello hello
we're really here to talk today about
hiring but we're gonna throw in a few
zooks 'as i know you guys want to want
to talk about that I know that's what
people are interested in I'm just gonna
go through we're gonna go through
Twitter and we're gonna see what people
are saying
Burton County welcome the Mahindra ass
will be supported as soon as somebody
wants to pay us 250 grand to port it or
somebody else look we're not gonna trash
talk is OU's I mean look if you're an
investor and tzuke's you got your money
back if you're a founder of tzuke's
you negotiated a payday for yourself if
you're an employer is excite you didn't
get but AM cares about the
employees anyway that's that's um we'll
see we'll see what happens uh I don't
know why I was on bottom
there that much I think yeah
damn you know Bezos wants what the view
on right OK ROCK accompany yourself
driving company you know and put it this
way if you're going to the space station
do you want a ride on a SpaceX Blue
Origin
no no nothing hey don't base us look you
know except for the 40 billion he lost
in the divorce he's great but let's see
let's just see what the Twitter staying
about Zuke's and we can't even go
through and I know I know that's what
you guys want to talk about so amazon
acquires self-driving startup dukes for
over 1.2 billion
so they raised nine hundred ninety
million so it is a little bit more than
they raised but my understanding is some
of the later investors had multiples on
their investment which means they're
guaranteed a payout you know if we go
back to two comma a eyes medium you guys
can see this is what this is what I said
in October um so you know it's not it's
not quite as bad as we will have it the
easiest when they're shut down the
employees there will be reabsorbed into
Google Cruz will be in the middle when
they're shut down the employees there
will attempt to be absorbed into GM &
Zuke's let's just say I'm glad I don't
work there right if you're tzuke's
employee you're now an Amazon employee
working at Amazon all right all right
all right so three points X oh my god
the car manufacturers locking me out the
car manufacturers locking me out look do
I even have to talk about this again can
you guys in the comments say what I'm
gonna say to that person who'll always
ask this question oh no oh no Toyota's
gonna lock me out Honda's gonna lock me
out um sug means never having to say
you're sorry yeah all right um so yeah I
mean you're you're you're now a you know
an Amazon employee you know what not as
bad not as bad as Drive that AI but uh I
mean it really comes down to no I wasn't
pissed when I saw zoogs got it quiet
about that it's not it's not that
surprising right and I've always said
it's not that Zuke's has nothing it's
that the whole idea doesn't make sense
our girl I think has now thank you
oh you know I gave I gave tzuke's props
those videos when they came out you know
they started to explain it like like
engineers is zooks worth a billion
dollars well they put nine hundred
ninety million into it so a one extra
turn a one exit so when you look at a DC
return multiple high start it's like a
classic 101 X 2 X less than max let's
see if I can
don't know how to find it
VC returned mostly though we're here to
talk about hiring for come AI easier
time I don't know you know what to be
honest hating on hating on the good good
for Zuke's I hope everyone there got got
the outcome they wanted I mean if I woke
up and I was an Amazon employee know
there's worse things there's definitely
worse things percent of investments by
VC return there's like a chart
percentage of investments by
I saw a really good pie chart that
explained that we just got it we're just
out here what yeah perfect VC fund
return on investment right
so 50% of the company's return less than
one xDrive that AI is here
zooks is here and then these five
percent of the companies that that the
VCS are super happy they invest in it
these are these are they these are the
big-name tech companies and these really
heavy seas make all of their money so
yeah
1.2 billion well let's see we can find
stuff about that deal so it's possible
that like so zukes raised basically they
raised a 790 million in their earlier
rounds they were trying to raise a 700
million dollar round they only raised
200 of those 700 million in convertible
notes so let's see if we can find
something I think oh there was a word
no there's nothing if I search resume to
be see multiple
9:55
what ratchet is what
yeah due to ratchets on later rounds
I've never heard this before but yeah
the company raised 1 billion in equity
and convertible debt investors are
basically gonna make their money back
and some will make a positive return ah
while the pre-money valuation was 2.7
billion in 2008 those investors know I
mean look it's oh it's a large
acquisition right do I personally care
about Dukes you know they've just been
with the story for a long time so it's
nice to see the story arc of tzuke's is
a story arc that we've been following so
it's good to bring nice closure to
everybody what's our plan for qtt with
us I just I just made this nice change
to UI which helps improve the
interaction between UI dot C and model
dot C but mostly what we're here to talk
about today is hiring for filming yeah
unless there are there any last
questions you can see there was some
interesting research coming on Twitter I
searched this morning and I saw some
interesting stuff uh yeah you know myth
Tesla leads autonomy right like some
totally fake oh yeah why doesn't
count
AI on there and you wonder would have
expected us to become a I um coming I
could do mostly what Tesla so I could do
on a smartphone
two cameras zookas team was highly
regarded as crashing well what do I
think of this deal how about this
they're a real thing to think about this
deal is Bezos lost 40 billion in a
divorce no concern for comma the concern
for comma here's here's what I would be
concerned if I was comma if tomorrow the
auto OEMs fired all their CEOs and put
in software people that would be like oh
well comma was good while it lasted
the good news is that's never gonna
happen actually another another bit of
news which is kind of interesting so if
you guys heard me rip on Nvidia in the
in the third or Tesla podcast
so this this story came out
mercedes-benz an Nvidia partner to bring
software-defined vehicles to market in
so Nvidia's chips are extremely
overpriced they're trying to get like
$500 to put their stuff in the car
mobilize about $50 , in huge quantities
is about $50 as well Nvidia is 500 so
what cars can support actual $500 costs
for an add-on well the Mercedes s-class
all right and that's the car that is
going to come to in 2024 not that set
rim a quiere Mac is also how much is a
rim at car does their Mac actually sell
cars it's it's hard to keep in my head
which one of these are scams in which
one of them are not scams just from
Excel design innovation oh yeah that
type of car do they how many cars have
they sold it starts at like Rimac lucid
Faraday future
Vivian some of them are scams some of
them are good what's that of the one
that has like five cars and their lineup
but hasn't actually shipped any cars yet
I rode in the Faraday future wasn't that
once in a scam they had one car they
showed it to me I sat on it we did a
launch hardware I seemed pretty nice the
software and I saw there's a little
thing on the window it's like a window
is little LCD screen nickel and nickel
is the one that like oh we announced
five cars but um are you planning on
expanding my product fleet want you buy
a comic too bro yeah the new medium
poster coming from our head of research
our head of alpha pilot and our new CEO
yeah yeah yeah so did you see anything
okay
um where else what else did I want to
talk about I said I wanted to talk about
something else oh oh this is kind of
interesting too today my software update
the model 3 also asked to start
recording on the interior camera alright
alright Tesla
we'll see we'll see when you I've always
bet the Tesla's gonna come out with
driver monitoring before they have fsd I
will see if that is true or not but if
anyone like to bet me ten thousand
dollars on that I'm down to take that
back before Tesla has FSD when they say
you cannot pay attention during their
commute Tesla will add camera based
driver monitoring penny would like to
bet ten grand on that roundabout ten
grand oh yeah this so um I'm gonna call
right now that there's a 50% chance that
this car ends up running open toilet now
you say George um how is this car gonna
end up running open pilot have you been
in talks with Mercedes and NVIDIA and
the answer to that is of course not but
what's gonna happen as they approach
this date the software is not gonna be
done it's not gonna have millions of
miles of real Road testing Mercedes is
gonna take it out they're gonna complain
to Nvidia about you know all those
normal mats the neural nets you know um
so what's gonna end up happening is
they're not really gonna have a choice
they're gonna have someone in the team
2020 probably even 2022 is gonna have is
gonna have a comma device in their car
I'm gonna be like you know this cold
open-source so we could probably get it
to run um and they will and the rest
will be history so that's I gave it a
50% chance that this Mercedes actually
ends up running you're not running up in
Thailand Europe is important tell me
more about this common needs Europe to
succeed tell me what do you mean what do
I not do for Europe yeah we don't I
don't need right what do I need to
succeed software engineers that's what I
need do we hire people from yeah
absolutely
um if we can the visa situation is a
little difficult right now but um yeah
we have a whole bunch of people from
Europe who came here now yeah I mean
that's a separate thing right do we hire
European software engineers absolutely
absolutely brilliant software engineers
in Europe do I somehow need to go to the
European market in order to succeed no I
have more data than I know what to do
with right now all we need right now is
software engineers and that brings me to
the main point of this post we're
getting very serious about hiring you
know we're happy to sponsor h-1b once
h-1bs are back to normal
h-1b J 101 if you I mean we've sponsored
on ones before as well
I've happen to be Sivan sir chef hold
also if you're in Europe and you're
interested in working for comma we have
an interesting announcement coming in a
bit but so the uncontained triangle of
success at comma our mission is to solve
self-driving cars while delivering
shippable intermediaries everything we
do is derive from that mission and as
the narrative unfolds it looks
increasingly like we will win alongside
Tesla and Mobil I um so like just talk
about how different that is from from
another company's post what guarantee
does someone have if they move across
the country or a world that you won't
fire them for no reason no one gets
fired for no reason if you're adding if
you're brilliant and adding tons of
value to kamo why would I fire you it
makes no sense if you're slacking and
causing trouble and requiring a lot of
management then yeah of course I'll fire
you
so what guarantee you have no guarantee
and if you're the kind of person who
needs guarantees
I don't think commas for you if you're
the kind of person is willing to comment
should never fire people
oh it's terrible but you know you got to
do it right because otherwise you'll end
up like Google with a lot of bad people
where all the good people left right um
yeah no I look one of the biggest things
for me if I'm thinking about how to you
know I'm thinking about a company I want
to look for I want to work for a company
full of great people right well you know
you can do a lot in the pre-screen but
you got to make sure the bar stays
really high not just for who you hire
but also for you keep around
I really don't recommend starting your
company oh you're the guy who borrowed
the part of the vote from it's come
pretty well it's come pretty well if
you'll see actually on your on your obd2
harness there was a little mistake and
how the voltage regulator was put on so
there's a bunch of bond wires and glue
that's gonna be fixed in all the
production ones , shouldn't fire people
and should give their product away for
free yes absolutely absolutely power to
the people workers of the world you know
alright um back in reality ah so we have
three teams we have the open Paulo team
the research team and the operations
team the open pallet team in builds and
maintains you open piles software the
research team builds the models the
operations team makes the product money
the website and the app so we can go
through a few of the jobs we're hiring
for you do not need to know anything in
particular about self-driving cars in
order to work here so if you think oh I
don't know about self-driving cars how
could I work here that doesn't matter we
don't care basically the two things we
really look for or be smart and be
motivated also know how to program
be smart be motivated and know how to
program competitors if you've done
competitions math competitions science
fairs competitive programming CTFs we're
interested that's a great thing to have
on your resume contributed to open
source projects have a great github easy
if you don't you know you should get
help with with stars on it and get up
that shows that you shouldn't you write
a lot of code right how do you get good
at writing code you write a lot of code
and then people who are people who are
good at like thinking things through and
don't just you know type Lots code all
our positions are full-time and on site
in downtown San Diego though if you're
in Europe they'll be they'll be an
announcement coming
you know to deal with that to do it is a
situation comic has full free lunch we
have a we have a chef who comes in and
cooks a hot lunch for everybody every
lunch we do if you're in the office feel
free to order will breed to go to dinner
almost every day so we're looking for
senior software engineers software
engineers to join the open pilot team
we're looking for m/l engineers and data
scientists looking for safety engineer
this is somebody who's gonna think about
safety some people think they can apply
for this and not be able to code no no
no you absolutely have to be able to
code you know someone's got to write
like the code to do when we do comma AED
and stuff infrastructure engineer tons
of tools need building I stopped driving
is largely an infrastructure problem ml
is largely an infrastructure problem so
yeah I mean you know being able to deal
with big data being able to dispatch
things to a thousand machines all that
stuff thousand cause you don't you have
a thousand machines full stack engineer
we're very excited about hiring this we
got to get somebody in to make the app
good to make the API good prime is
starting to become a real profit center
for the company well not quite yet
actually prime cost a ton of money but
soon prime will make money and we want
to make great quality experience for our
users we don't use kubernetes use docker
for a bunch of things communities
confusing
navigation designer so yes we will
eventually be adding navigation I into
open pilot open pilot needs to know
where you are going there's a lot a lot
of trolls in the comments today man you
know from what I heard Oh operations
assistant oh it's been changed yeah we
didn't talk about that one um
that one is uh this is really what we're
looking to get really really what guys
this year we've sold a lot more stuff we
started selling at a 3x increased in
revenue this year versus the same time
last year
I'd rather work at a big company where I
don't need high motivation it's great
it's great people select themselves out
but no I mean it's a problem and you
know I'm judging it a bit from you guys
in the comments - it's like we're
getting a lot we're getting a lot more
regions but they're just not from people
who are good not from people who would
hire uh yeah the bar is like really high
to solve these problems
look self-driving is gonna be solved by
20 geniuses it's not gonna be solved by
a thousand people it just I don't think
any research problems in history have
ever been solved that way alright you
have some like you know on the extreme
end you have things like the proof of
from Oz Last Theorem right which is
solved really by its one lone genius
it's one lone genius building on top of
a lot of other people's work and of
course you're always gonna be building
on top of other people's work that's how
any science or research or engineering
works but you know in reality there's
nothing self driving is gonna be solved
by 20 people and no a thousand computers
right if you believe in like an ml
solution to self-driving there's not
gonna be a lot of open pilot in and of
itself except for adding navigation to
it like the the whole UX and stuff is
kind of done like it can use some
refinement and stuff but like it's it's
there we have some good stuff as we
approach one point out
I'm brutally not you have to be brutally
honest look if you want to get anything
done in the world and you're being
dishonest you're only hurting yourself
[Music]
yeah I mean it's really the two things
that we look for fundamentally our
intelligence and motivation and then
both of those things generally overt I
mean there is some amount of there's
some amount of skill required like if
you can't program I wonder why you can't
program we don't hire remote employees
though like I said if you're in Europe
and you're looking announcement
announcement coming
I don't know I'm not sure this this
judging from the comments here I'm
really not sure that this yeah think
about it I'm gonna have to think about
like how where yeah the regions have
been getting worse right I was hoping as
we grew I was hoping as we grew and we
got more users and we do we have a lot
more attention now our google trends are
up but the quality of the candidates has
fallen ah so yeah I don't know I don't
really know what to do about this I
think maybe one of the things we can do
is start writing up a lot of technical
see I mean I don't know personally I
think a lot of education is just a
straight-up scam like what should you
study to prepare I almost don't care
like you should program and you should
practice programming but it's not like
it's studying right it's like it's
practicing way more than studying I
don't care if you memorized a book who
cares I thought what I think of what I
think of studying now
have you put 10,000 hours into
programming that's that makes you good
yeah I think I think maybe that's
something we can do we can start we can
start documenting our code better how a
lot of the stack works better writing
like high quality but somewhat dry
technical documentation I think I think
might help though
wooden buy create an open-source
community I'm gonna slap a foundation
label on it and incorporate it as a
non-profit what do you think that
changes man you know this is the the
cargo cult of business when people think
it's things like that
when will comma go in public never the
more i've the more i've looked into that
bearish on that so look the comma - sold
3x more than the yield if the products
keep increasing in the way they've been
increasing the thing about exponential
is it gets it gets real big real fast so
if this stuff works I'm thinking in a
few years even with our current we're a
consumer electronics company we're gonna
have really large cash flows and we do
a new sector
all right the the self-driving add-on
thing I'm an SRE can I apply any my
permission
apply we'll do it with Google phone
screen and we do a carbon challenge we
do well on those look it's a real uh
it's all merit-based man I don't care
what your title is I don't really care
that much what's on your resume shirts
are out of stock what's our current burn
rate negative bro it's negative because
we make money because we're profitable
company no I hate remote remotes parable
the only way to possibly get considered
for a moat is if you've contributed tons
of pull requests to open pilot and then
we can consider bringing you on but
there is no way we will hire someone new
for a remote position these people that
you hard to manage honestly I think a
lot of people who ask for a motive cuz
they want to slack off ah you thought
the purpose of a startup with the Byrne
VC as quickly as possible that's the old
so no decade is 2020 everything changed
why do work experience again how do you
get hub look alright you want work
experience show me like you open source
projects you made that are in use Wow
damn that's good that's good work
experience
um did our investors make money already
no I'll give them the money they want
their money back God doesn't owe money
back I'll give them just like Zuke's you
know how can comma to beat all these why
do you think they're my competition why
do you think Derek competition why do
you think why do you think we compete
with Amazon and Google we don't
I can't get a job in programming because
I can't sell myself can you help
yeah I've tried to be nicer in the
interviews I've tried to be nicer
oh yes going Joe Rogan oh that's gonna
get me a whole a whole lot of inbound
that I want all right yeah you know what
more technical stuff will show more
technical content this is what I've been
working on this week thinking envision
features right when you think and your
brain about driving you don't think
about you don't think of pictures
you think features so we have a great
vision model a bunch of coffees and then
we're building these models auto encoder
decoder you can you can visualize it all
we got to put that we gotta put that on
Twitter that looks cool I love impatient
model dynamics model hardware people I
mean maybe our new again if you do
hardware and you can also code yeah
we're interested if you just do hardware
and can't code and I don't think so
let's see oh yeah and this is kind of
like show you guys
so this is one of the things I've been
working on
so what this is here this is the how
this is the box that open pilot is using
in order to drive and this is a
visualization model from the vision
features so I trained an autoencoder
to take the vision features and bring
them back up to an image this is what it
looks like when it's a video you see how
that thing appeared there look at the
lane change so this is how open pilots
actually seeing the world
I mean we're gonna start doing a lot
more stuff what we think in these vision
features right you're gonna see
something interesting up here when a car
comes across yeah I know the auto
encoder doesn't perfectly capture it you
know the loss functions not perfect it's
not sampled it's averaged yeah well you
know it's decent here part of the
problem also is this a small model we
need big model I'll show you guys
another one
it's not one
it's not a VA II it's not variational
I'm not doing any sort of bit
restriction on it we're training the
vision model separately supervised and
then we just take the features and bring
them back to the image space
I'll show you guys another thing
what's holding back 0-8 a lot of work
yeah I love a lot of hard work we're
making some big changes to the models
we're getting the models ready for level
5 so you can give this a second to load
here
how's the simulator coming along this is
the simulator envision feature space
yeah I'm reading the comments yeah we
use a finite state machine for lane
change I'm not really sure how else
you'd do it
so we can actually move so like I can
here this is ways D so you move around
with WASD just like a video game so I
can like turn I can also strafe and this
is thinking envision future space
I'm sis is using a transformation model
inside of the space that open pilots
using to reason yeah I can also I can
also was D with a so if I don't use the
ml transform model all right whoops keep
on to
give this one a second to load this
one's actually using the image and just
doing a normal augmentation I can't
drive I got to turn so slowly
yeah but we don't actually go back to
the RGB image when we do any of the
training yeah we are
we had a big we had an off-site last
week we are level 5 summit where we
discuss very seriously what it's gonna
take to get the well we settled on level
3 there's some chance we think Tesla is
gonna be first to level 3 with us in
second we think there's some chance
we'll beat them yeah we can augment the
Layton space basically it's not
something I mean it's the wrong thing
but it was something it's better than
Cruz I think I've said that way before
their acquisition too I think the bigger
problem is and then known as ooks and
Cruz look similar so what are the
outcomes for tzuke's employees they're
gonna look similar to Amazon employees
LSD slam uses photometric losses the
comma - is not that good at photometric
loss very good at geometric loss but
yeah everything we're doing is is
geometric not photometric oh my god the
more camera question no no I never
planned to add another camera
never never we're always gonna be on one
camera I'm getting paid by big one
camera to make sure we only ever stay on
one camera don't see us 21 yeah you want
to order our comma too so bad what are
you currently doing to address what am i
doing
but normally she's our gonna get better
yeah they're gonna get better oh there's
a few problems with it we're doing a
bunch of tests tonight if I go 2-0
cameras big one camera I won't pay me
I've pointed out of three cameras all
pointing the same direction with similar
field of view so that what you guys want
well that'd make you all happy uh what I
most shirts being stock again bro I
think shirts didn't make us enough money
I think shirts weren't a big profit
center for the company
we need profit Center I love profit
ah why are we so open because no one
listens to us anyway you know and that's
gonna be the real joke and that's gonna
be the real joke when all this stuff is
over you could be open you can say the
truth people don't listen they hear what
they want to hear their inner echo
chambers you know a lot of them have
yeah when you're invested when you put
commas been around for five years right
if you're at Wave low and you put ten
fifteen years your life into this in
your link are you gonna be like you
don't wake up one day and be like you
know guys I don't actually think this is
the right way to do it
what else can we talk about about hire
we have a hacker rank challenge and we
have a we have the programming challenge
and I speed prediction challenge it's
still actually a surprisingly good
challenged it's just a video and the
question is can you from the video
figure out how the car is driving how
fast it's going just how fast it's going
Wow Wow looks so weird with the old view
before HDR Kumbi yeah just output the
speed if you're the type of person who
chooses where to work based on free
drinks and good food and I don't know
man I don't know there's no name for the
Dukes is not a public company there's no
name for the stock of tzuke's this is
cool yo let's look at this one but in ml
transform land never mind
can't find that one again would have
been cool to look at that one an m/l
transformed land though we could look at
that same we do look at that same route
but instead of looking at it through the
eyes of a camera you can look at it
through the eyes of the model uh yeah
flow why you think I want a miniature
you think you think how I've gotta be a
little more precise than that don't you
think
um modafinil is a schedule for
controlled substance
Adrina Phil is not that my grief Anila
miss Polly still true is that 3d model a
custom library what reading all yeah I
don't know guys I'm bearish on the
streams
that's why I haven't been streaming in a
bed I'm bearish on the stream being
useful for hiring where's the hacker
rank email an email in a resume are the
hacker and cost us like a dollar so I
think we ask you a few pre-screen
questions first so you feel worth a
dollar
most people worth a dollar yeah I'm
bearish I'm bearish on the utility of
these streams maybe that was just an
error of comment yeah that's over we're
a real company now we got we got
executives we got three divisions we got
profit you know I'm still the same guy
hey you know like gonna people don't
change right yeah hire some recruiters
put people to a process get some
bureaucracy up in here what y'all think
can you know click the simulator sounds
like yeah I know you like hearing from
you but the question is like ask not
what these streams can do for you but
what these streams can do for me stream
is important for selling products I
don't need to sell more products we're
profitable we're making cash making cash
boys yeah take a look come for Shopify
let me just look it over a little bit
and make sure everything on the screens
okay you don't like we don't like
leaking information about our customers
but as long as it's fully anonymized
data it's all good
yeah buddy I gotta have money
look at that money look at money um yeah
so that's that's enough to run the
company
enough to uh yeah we're still selling
phone meetings thousand bucks how many I
slash services you could buy a meeting
wonder if investors don't best until
they raise again so the investors own
equity in this company um and its
preferred chair so they're totally
welcome to sell it at any time I think
right now it'd be pretty easy if they
wanted to turn a profit to sell it to
somebody else
so welcome to go
yeah if you're applying for a job here
think about which division you'd like to
apply for it's we've three divisions and
we have a different interview process
for each of the divisions we have the
Open File division the research division
and the operations division why don't
you open a small crowdfunding for a
small portion of your equity but I don't
need money why do I need money why do
you live in the bare a dying place
I mean why don't you make cryptocurrency
see you're why I don't do streams man
you're why I don't do streams
we do hire interns uh the bar is almost
higher for interns not similar the bar
so if you're really good you hire isn't
intentional here's kind of it yours kind
of like how I think about it right you
got all the column employees you can put
them in a ranked list and then you have
the mean of that list right we want to
hire new people that bring up the mean
that's how you make sure our company is
continually improving am I looking for
marketing why would I do marketing I
don't need more sales and more engineers
to solve self-driving cars remember the
mission of the company is to solve
self-driving cars while delivering
shippable intermediaries right so what
we need to solve something cars well
that list there we really need someone
we really need someone to build out
navigation any navigation is gonna be a
big thing for the next year we have a
whole back-end mapping effort we need to
hire people for well so do more
engineers solve the problem more
engineers are only good if you have
different things that need doing right
if you know you know the same right
three women can't have a baby you know
if one women if one woman can have a
baby in nine months three women can of a
baby in three months so I mean this is
true if you're having one baby but three
women can't have three babies in nine
months right whereas one woman would
take 27 and she probably not even gonna
wait a little bit but see that's I mean
that's what I mean if you can if you can
break it up into different like tasks
that need doing in order underneath the
big umbrella task of solving
self-driving cars then having more
software engineers definitely helps
right another way to think about this is
on dolls law right like problems are
parallelizable to an extent
this is a classic it's um like it's
gonna bad money and stuff
Oh simulations are good for testing not
good for training simulation is doing to
succeed if you train a simulation say
the stuff all the time don't wanna so I
write it all up write it all up the real
solution to self-driving which I pull uh
Sebastian thrown and start at Udacity
course for self-driving right like
Sebastian throws like Shimon was gonna
take him in the ten years to solve I'm
out I'll just train the people who did
it right what I think about mapillary
getting bought by Facebook well that's
the end of mapillary right who bought
who bought open open the street cam that
was bought by some company - it's sad
you know these things just go to die
where two semi trucks fall for me what
about semi trucks but yeah um the the
whole point of the company is the
mission so think about how well I mean
you can see kind of what my breakdown is
I'm pretty open about how we do it um
we're trying to be the alphago of
self-driving the thing about alphago is
entering the self-driving car market now
all right what self-driving car market
what cell driving car market are they
entering it's not market
well we're like the biggest market that
there's no there's no where's this where
is this market what are you what are you
buying right are you guys happy Tesla's
making a lot more off those off those
fall self-driving yep
but zooks isn't in a market zooks is a
research lab
I want to tap into ourselves by
commenting she'll talk over there
I don't care about average I don't care
about ours what is the average skill
level hey look at the code right I think
it's quite high yeah it would boost my
revenue yes but I don't need more
revenue I mean I need more talented
software engineers right like I didn't
come here and win you know
oh it's winning is winning just out of
out of out of phase in the world right I
want to have a job at Google where I do
nothing with my life and I tweak rest
endpoints to make sure we have
accessibility for cripples in
Czechoslovakia right like that's that's
that's really yeah that's what it comes
down to that's what these that's what
these you do not think up these
companies
no no but yeah yeah like like why is why
is the software engineering talent their
software and talent also goes to finance
they paid you play it a scam game like
you're playing a game with you take you
take the money and and oh look I'm
making all this money it's all fake
right more exposure equals more
engineers well so I was hoping that I
was hoping that this year it seems to
not be that true but you need to know
about slam before it now I didn't know
about slam four years ago I told me what
I hired myself right I don't I'm not I'm
not gonna ask you if you know slam in
any in any in any interview
what did most current engineers come
from reach and reach out I'll do it
right like you just you know it's the
top one percent of the people who apply
but none like okay half the people half
the people who we want accept the offer
and yeah that's where they come from
right what's the first question I ask
what's the derivative of x squared
not all engineers want to be an engineer
don't be an engineer do what you want as
I'm paid a 1.2 billion what do I think
zukes is actually worth what's hard
thing to value if you're thinking about
future returns of Zeus's business model
it's worth negative money if you're
thinking about repurposing this
technology for making your deliveries 20
percent faster than to be honest it
might actually be worth 1.2 billion to
Amazon it might be worth more right if
you could figure out how to get all
Amazon if you could do Amazon deliveries
20% more efficient that's easily worth
the money so I don't know if this
technology can be repurposed for that
I don't like Ross I think it's build
libraries not frameworks I think Ross is
a framework and not a library we get a
lot of the same stuff we know of a
library called serial comma die slash
cereal I know github it's again out of
cereal and it does multiple rastas we
use cap and proto for the binary packing
format we used to use zmq for message
passing but zmq puts the bite to the
kernel which is slow so now we are head
of open pilot wrote a custom one that
uses a ring buffers in shared memory
mr. everything a master timeout you need
solve leak code how to keep the model so
small they're growing and getting big
they're getting big yeah that we got it
we got to change it right now the models
are being stored on disk is float32 but
they're only being used the way to only
be used by the GP is float16 so we can
know we can change that
I don't know what Elite code 500 problem
is the spammers are yeah yeah yeah I
don't know maybe use the format of these
streams right I'm gonna do it on Twitch
I did it a lot to just kind of blow off
steam kind of talk but maybe that
doesn't attract the best sort of
audience so I'll have to do a bit of a
bit of reflection on how to get the
right to other people and maybe the
right sort of people are out there and
they're watching this there's not
commented or they they click around on
it they read the comments
when do I think , will reach level 3 3
years that was kind of that there's kind
of the consensus the offside level 5 is
still too far away to think about we
were all pretty convinced that it's more
than five years away but level three can
be reached significantly sooner it's an
achievable goal and it's what we're
pushing towards we need to get our
models to be so reliable in fact when
you're in level 3 level 2 has a
completely different safety paradigm
from level 3 in level 2 we don't trust
the models we have lots of stuff after
the models to prevent like high torques
on the steering wheel for example right
and this is good in a level 2 system
because we expect if a high torques
require the user code but at level 3
where you can't rely on the user at
least can't rely on the user quickly
that stuff becomes a lot less relevant
so in three years world comma P well
you're a spammer so you don't get an
answer I was gonna give you an answer
but you spammed so now you get a timeout
and no answer yes
we're not working remotely we never
worked remotely you know I'm 30 years
old right a lot of people here pretty
young lucky for you I'm good at me the
periscope era was awesome
it's for a different thing right like
we're not here to do we're not here to
I'm not here to promote the product I'm
here to promote the company I'm here to
promote put it this way you show me you
show me that uh you're great engineer
you show me you're great engineer and
you're skeptical that comas gonna win
and you're skeptical that we're gonna
win
self-driving cars do my programming
challenge they were programming
challenge you the hacker and get a
perfect score it's easy and then I'll do
it through a phone call with you the 30
minute phone call with you and if at the
end of the 30 minute phone call I
haven't convinced you I mean I'm sure I
will I'm it's if you truly think about
this space free of preconceptions and
you look at what's going to be required
to solve this problem your and your
burst and you know the direction ml has
been going the direction of the legacy
self-driving car companies have been
going direction Tesla has been going I'm
sure after 30 minute phone call I'll
convince you
redundancy is something to think about
after the software is good enough most
of the problems now are not caused by
hardware failures but by Stauffer
factors I just have to be people within
the US know we're happy to get you here
we're happy to look if you're super
talented we'll make it work we'll figure
out how to not remote not remote I'm not
gonna go that far but perhaps we'll have
an office outside the US
if DISA things become an issue or if we
can sponsor your visa we're happy to do
it
honestly why you should work at comma of
Google pays 3x well so two things about
that
one assure Google salaries our Google
salaries are 2x higher um but your
Google equities not gonna 10x alright
your Google equity is there's no 10x
growth for Google there is very easily
10x growth for comma so the OP side
could potentially be much larger working
here instead of Google um so from a
straight monetary perspective you can
make arguments for comma above Google
but if you're into the straight monetary
arguments you know it's boring the
second reason is what are you gonna do
at Google right do you think you're
gonna build something revolutionary or
do you think you're gonna look into a
Google Docs bug on ie6 and have to go
through three stages of code review and
you know sit through sit through three
meetings every day and if that's what
you want to do with your life and that's
what it's worth to get oh I'm getting
double the money in the bank right now
you know I started as a risk right happy
I know if you're talented with the
amount of equity you get you stand to
make a lot more money here
if you're not interested in software
development please go argue you'd have
an impact but honestly you will make
more money probably too if we succeed if
comma actually gets to level three
within three years yo yo don't make more
money game for what Google do I have any
advice for early age stage startups shut
down while you still can't give the
money back to your VCS tell them sorry
about the 30% haircut and be like I'm
out bro
what if google buys , Google's not
buying , not selling the Google himself
to Google two billion two billion or
sell to Google then I'll take the money
and start a pasta
that's an hour-long stream I'll go back
to working a little bit it's almost
lunchtime product design Menkes not
really I'm pretty much can you code
let's hear from someone in the
background they got things that don't
like it a distractor it's bad enough
that I'll distract our boss
we used to flow I don't know I know
there's the movement all I gotta use
fight towards yeah I think cross is nice
Google may take that offer yeah Google
takes that offer yeah I'll go start
apostrophe with the money after I you
know and get rid of my handcuffs after a
year right two billion two billion and
you know what you want to talk about I'm
not just gonna talk with you got a wire
two million first two million to come to
the come to the table the hours do I
work for week 200 bro 100 how many hours
am i awake it's more than a hundred
that's right always working work is life
what is a posture if you do it well the
same thing is common are we hiring
front-end dance um it depends yeah maybe
if you think you can qualify full stack
will hire you if your full stack with
more emphasis on the front end will hire
you if you're good with UI stuff will
hire you so yeah if your if your react
JavaScript sure
how good is Luke's compared to Kama it's
totally different I don't care if
full-stack does not require any ml you
won't be touching any of the ml stuff
you're looking for graduates or senior
experience levels I don't care um yeah
but we have an intern here it's 20 it's
genius
you know if there were if there were
five more people like him I'd uh give
them all full-time jobs
what type of job security can you offer
[Laughter]
look here's the thing about that
question you actually have quite decent
job security but if you're the kind of
person who's interested in job security
you completely
you'd never you'd never work here you'd
never you'd never like like we're trying
to do something new right we're not
trying to maintain Google Docs for ie6
here with respect to like to ask the
question seriously all right this is
saying look if your program doesn't
finish in one second it won't finish in
two if the program doesn't finish in two
seconds we won't finish in four four
eight eight sixteen so on so forth , has
been around for five years we're a
profitable company we've raised 8.1
million dollars which is laughable
compared to what we have so yeah I mean
the company's not going anywhere
so with respect to job security like
that'd be worried about the company
disappearing I wouldn't worry about that
if you're worried about getting fired
that's a personal thing between you and
your skills um you know I mean there's a
job security question like is comma
shutting down next week I am I going to
announce tomorrow sorry guys you
couldn't raise any money you're all
bought by Amazon no of course not all
right that's an hour thank you for
joining coming I slash jobs you want to
win three years to level three being a
part of the winning team get rich change
the world that's right
see like